Hi, this is Jorge Benllach, I'm a sculptor, and I'm here today because I'm going to try to show you how to do, like, a boat, with some kind of fishermans on, and a big fish.
It's like a caricature of this, you know, the poor fisherman that tried to make the big one...to catch the big one.
It's like me, I'm...I'm a....I'm a fisherman, that's why I know.
And ah...you know, I'm a boat owner, too.
I know what I'm talking about.
Anyway, it's going to be a very interesting and fun figurine, that you can make it for some kind of...for your parents, for some friends, and you can personalize also, putting some kind of objects, or making like a caricature of a look-alike of the two characters that I am going to put in there.
This is going to be like a basic exaggerated and caricature boat, with a...with two fishermans on it and one big fish.
The materials that we are going to use, they are water-based clay, and I'm going to use the gray one.
And not many tools, one base, one string to cut the clay, these two pieces of wood in order to make the slabs even, a roller pin, and maybe this pick in order to make some cuttings.
And probably this piece of policspan, in order to make like a support of the base, in order to avoid the boat collapse.
Later I will tell you that this cannot be there, when it dry off.
We have to take it off.
That's why I'm going to wrap with paper.
And, you will see.